https://www.nice-racks.com/policies/

Loading... Please wait...
Payments
All credit card payments are charged at the time the order is placed.
All shipping quotes are for Ground shipments within the 48 Continental U.S. states. Please contact us for shipping quotes outside the continental U.S.
Shipping
Each and every rack is handmade-to-order and the average turnaround time for Nice-Racks handmade studio racks varies, but is typically 1 1/2 to 2 1/2 weeks before your new rack ships.
Accessories and electronics orders normally ship the same day if ordered before 3PM EST, otherwise within 24-48 hours of placing your order. In the event an item is unavailable or backordered, we will notify you immediately. If you order a custom rack along with any accessories, everything ships together once the studio rack is complete, however some larger accessories may need to ship separately.
All shipping quotes are for Ground shipments within the 48 Continental U.S. states. Please contact us for shipping quotes outside the continental U.S.
Returns
You may return most new, unused items within 30 days of delivery for a full refund. We'll also pay the return shipping costs if the return is a result of our error (you received an incorrect or defective item, etc.), or if the item is damaged during shipping.In most cases, we will process your refund immediately upon the item's return, however, you should expect to receive your refund within 1-2 weeks of our receiving the returned item.  This time period includes the time it may take for your bank or credit card provider to process our refund request.If you need to return an item, simply login to your account, view the order using the "Complete Orders" link under the My Account menu and click the Return Item(s) button. We'll notify you via e-mail of your refund once we've received and processed the returned item. Or contact me directly at sales@nice-racks.com.Product Availability
Availability is not guaranteed: Email us to check stock before placing your order.  We attempt to only show available products but sometimes products sell out before we can update the product webpage.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Baystate Music collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.nice-racks.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Baystate Music.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the siteplace an order and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number,
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Baystate Music collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our SiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactionsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To send periodic emailsThe email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website\'s own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Changes to this privacy policy
Baystate Music has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
As of August 2018, Minwax has changed their selection of water-based colors and …
Sign up to our newsletter
Your Name:
Your Email:
All prices are in USD.
Copyright 2020 Nice-Racks.
Sitemap |
Shopping Cart Software by BigCommerce
